<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on tillepille</title>
    <link>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on tillepille</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>tl@mindlink.de (Tim Schrumpf)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>tl@mindlink.de (Tim Schrumpf)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 16:19:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tillepille.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get a Job</title>
      <link>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/how-to-get-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 16:19:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>tl@mindlink.de (Tim Schrumpf)</author>
      <guid>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/how-to-get-a-job/</guid>
      <description>My way until now My dad is a self-employed IT-Consultant, mainly focused on private persons to small businesses, everything from hardware and network/telephone wiring to software and service. Also some cozy, never-think-about mail and webhosting. I helped here and there, mainly focused on the hosting and everything related to Apple.
I started computer science in 2014 at the TU Dortmund, right next to my city, started to slow down my pace sometime but doing all the things, I saw some sense in for the practical future: Distributed Systems, Software Architecture, programming classes and even functional programming in Haskell, but really tuck away from the heavy math stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speedtests</title>
      <link>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/speedtests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 21:30:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>tl@mindlink.de (Tim Schrumpf)</author>
      <guid>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/speedtests/</guid>
      <description>about browsers und speedtests
Internet of Speeds Since I got a Gigabit Connection at home over DOCSIS 3.1 (at least Downsteam, Upstream is 50MBit), i like too see how fast my internet is. When your alone there aren‘t really many use cases where you need such a fast connection.
But beside seeing the speeds on the interface of the router, eventually it was difficult to test the actual speeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 21:29:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>tl@mindlink.de (Tim Schrumpf)</author>
      <guid>https://tillepille.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;write a blog!&amp;rdquo; they said&amp;hellip; Okay, so here I am. Or at least my blog.
Since I&amp;rsquo;m a computer science student, i do it on github rather than on tumblr&amp;hellip; As you can see, powered with hugo and currently no Pipeline.. :(</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>